In this section of the course, we are not going to talk about coding. Instead,
we're going to talk
about mindsets. You're learning how to code because maybe you want to build an
app for you and your
friends or even you might want to build an entire business and replace your 9
to 5. Whatever this
is you're trying to achieve, my goal with these following lessons of this
chapter is to give you
the entire mindset that I've acquired in the past six years in order for you to
achieve your goals.
We're going to talk about things like how to turn your idea into a reality as
fast as possible so
you don't burn out. We're going to talk about marketing principles for you to
build a profitable
business and we're going to talk about how to become self-driven, how to easily
find
motivation so you want to show up every day and do the work. Let's begin.